# Jordan Heath

jordanheath945@gmail.com || C: 647-919-9780 || LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-heath-aa757819b/

## **SUMMARY**

Amiable IT Support Specialist ready to work with technical and non-technical personnel to rapidly discern root causes and correct disruptive issues. Consistent provider of friendly internal worker and external customer interactions. Combined deep technical knowledge with amicable demeanor to support both exceptional resolution and satisfaction metrics.

## **SKILLS**

- Communication
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and Outlook)
- Multi-tasking
- Flexible
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork

- Data Analysis
- Interpersonal Skills
- Business Strategy
- Articulate and well-spoken
- IT
- Computer Coding

## **EXPERIENCE**

HCMS | Toronto, ON

## **Cleaning Supervisor**

07/2015 - Current

- Accounting, invoicing, processing payments, and accounts payable of cleaning supplies
- Create and manage a webpage for company to facilitate social engagement with customers looking for cleaning services
- Suggest additional services that can be provided to customers through expansion of cleaning tools such as floor scrubbers, carpet cleaners, floor buffers, and microfibre products
- Assist in cleaning and detail work
- Coordinate additional cleaning days and plan deep cleaning procedures
- Assist in job training new staff and inspecting quality of work

#### Sunfresh International Juice Inc | Port St. Lucie, FL

#### Office Administrator

05/2012 - 06/2014

- Administer and maintain daily front office operations, including greeting clients, responding to phone calls, and performing billing tasks
- Slashed cost of office supplies by 15% through negotiating prices with suppliers and maintaining appropriate stock levels to avoid shortages
- Create distribution agreement for the CEO in compliance with legal policies and procedures while sorting and distributing mails and calls to appropriate personnel
- Control all office expenses and costs for employees, including quarterly report metrics for travel, expenses, and housing
- Developed and implemented a filing system that would maximize organization and introduce effective scheduling techniques

## Sears Carpet & Upholstery Care | Toronto, ON

# **Carpet Cleaning Assistant**

06/2009 - 03/2011

- Facilitate billing and job quoting
- Review accounting and ensure revenue and expenses are correct
- Review job calendar to ensure efficient travel paths for jobs
- Assist in cleaning and wrapping up equipment
- Inspect and maintain equipment quality to prevent hazards and delays due to equipment replacement
- Give the best opportunity to up sale and provide additional services to customer if they are willing to accept

## **EDUCATION**

Honours Bachelor of Arts, University of Toronto

Program: Double Major - Diaspora and Transnational Studies/Canadian Studies

09/2018 - 04/2022

- 3.7/4.0 Annual GPA in final year of program
- Recipient of Reubens Wells Leonard Scholarship for Canadian Studies for maintaining a or over 3.0 GPA in Canadian Studies based courses

Certificate: Cloud Computing

2022 - 06/2023

 Progressing toward completing an IT certificate at the University of Toronto starting this August and finishing July of 2023

Certificate: Full Stack Web Development/Coding

2022 - 11/2022

- Progressing toward completing a full-stack web development program at the University of Toronto starting September 2022 and finishing November of 2022

## **VOLUNTEERING**

**Software For Love - HR** 

**Content Creator Volunteer** 

5/01/2021 - 8/31/2021

**Heritage Skills Development Centre** 

**Graphic Designer (Intern/Volunteer)** 

5/01/2020 - 8/31/2020

Peel District School Board - Black Youth Success

Online Tutor/Homework Support Volunteer

9/13/2019 - 1/25/2020